valotalive.com 2016-10-31

# security

                               Valotalive Privacy Policy
                              Last updated the 24th of May 2016
Our customers’ privacy is a high priority to Valotalive. So we’ve developed a Privacy
Policy that covers the basics of how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your
information. Please take a moment to take a look at our privacy practices and ​    let us
know​  if you have any questions.
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for ​    www.valotalive.com​
                                                                               . This
privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify
you of the following:
           1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through
              the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
           2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
           3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
              information.
           4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have
access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct
contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted
us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our
organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you
about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the
following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given
on our website:
  • See what data we have about you, if any.
  • Change/correct any data we have about you.
  • Have us delete any data we have about you.
  • Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive
information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and
transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock
icon on your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of
the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we
also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to
perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access
to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store
personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Registration
In order to use our services, a user must first complete the registration form. During
registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email
address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our
site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide
demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not
required.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must
provide contact information (i.e company name and shipping address) and
financial information (i.e company invoicing details or credit card number &
expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your
orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact
you.
Third-Party Payment Processor
We use a third party payment processor, Stripe, for all payments. Valotalive does not
store credit card details and instead relies on Stripe for this.
Cookies
When you use Valotalive, we may store "cookies", “tags” or “scripts”, which are
strings of code, on your computer. We and our analytics Service Providers (like
Google​ ) use those cookies to collect information about your visit and your use of our
Website or Services. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of
our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way
linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Sharing
At times we may make certain information available to our strategic partners that
work with Valotalive to provide content and services that Valotalive markets. This
is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact
information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These

parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the
purpose of providing these services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Our privacy policy governs our own site.
Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of
such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and
to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable
information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on
this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should ​
                                                                       contact us
immediately.
                                          Valota Oy
                        Keilaranta 16 B, Espoo Regus Business Centre
                                    02150 Espoo, Finland
                                      VAT FI2503041-7
                                    www.valotalive.com
